mobiloans.com 2016-04-07

# Privacy Policy

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do. 

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include: 

  * Social Security number and income
  * Account balances and payment history
  * Credit history and credit scores

All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons MobiLoans, LLC chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing. 

For our everyday business purposes – such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus 

Does MobiLoans, LLC share?

YES

Can you limit this sharing?

NO

For our marketing purposes – to offer our products and services to you 

Does MobiLoans, LLC share?

YES

Can you limit this sharing?

NO

For joint marketing with other financial companies 

Does MobiLoans, LLC share?

YES

Can you limit this sharing?

NO

For our affiliates everyday business purposes – information about your transactions and experiences 

Does MobiLoans, LLC share?

NO

Can you limit this sharing?

WE DO NOT SHARE

For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness 

Does MobiLoans, LLC share?

NO

Can you limit this sharing?

WE DO NOT SHARE

For our affiliates to market to you

Does MobiLoans, LLC share?

NO

Can you limit this sharing?

WE DO NOT SHARE

For non-affiliates to market to you

Does MobiLoans, LLC share?

YES

Can you limit this sharing?

YES

  * Call 877-836-1518 – our menu will prompt you through your choice(s);
  * Log in to your account at [www.mobiloans.com](http://www.mobiloans.com/) and click on the “Manage Profile” tab and select “Contact Preferences”; or
  * Contact us via email: [support@mobiloans.com](mailto:support@mobiloans.com).

Please note:  
If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information as soon as the same day that you apply for a line of credit. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice. 

However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.

How does MobiLoans, LLC protect my personal information? 

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings. We also maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards (i.e., computer virus protection software, firewalls, 128 bit Secure Socket Layer). Only authorized employees have access. 

How does MobiLoans, LLC collect my personal information? 

We collect your personal information, for example, when you 

  * Apply for a line of credit
  * Give us your income information
  * Provide employment information
  * Provide account information
  * Give us your contact information

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies. 

Why can’t I limit all sharing? 

Federal law gives you the right to limit only 

  * Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes-information about your creditworthiness
  * Affiliates from using your information to market to you
  * Sharing for non-affiliates to market to you.

Financial and nonfinancial companies related by common ownership or control. 

  * MobiLoans, LLC has no affiliates.

Financial and nonfinancial companies not related by common ownership or control.

  * Non-affiliates we share with can include direct marketing companies for application resell, direct mail and other purposes.

A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you. 

  * Our joint marketing partners include financial institutions, credit card companies, partners that promote our products, pre-paid debit card providers and other lending companies. 

As part of our credit underwriting and information collection process, we will consider bank account information provided by you and we may detect additional bank accounts under your ownership. We also may collect and consider information about you from non-credit reporting agency data providers, including, for example, information about your location and the location of your mobile devices and publicly available information about you. 

Updating your information: If you need to update the personal information you have given us, log in to your account at [www.mobiloans.com](http://www.mobiloans.com/) and click on the “Manage Profile” tab and select “Edit Your Application” or call 877-836-1518 to speak to an account representative. 

“Do not track”: When someone visits the MobiLoans website, a cookie is placed on the visitor’s computer (if the visitor accepts cookies). The cookie we place on your computer does not contain any of your personally identifiable information. MobiLoans advertises its products and services on websites that you may visit, and MobiLoans uses service providers to place such advertisements. Those service providers (such as Google, Microsoft or Yahoo) may use cookies placed on your computer to show you advertisements for MobiLoans services on other websites. You can opt-out from service providers’ and/or marketers’ use of cookies in this manner by visiting each service provider’s advertising opt-out page or by utilizing “do not track” functionality in your web browser. If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the MobiLoans website, you will not be able to subscribe to the service offerings on the MobiLoans website. 

Changes to this privacy policy: If we make material changes to this privacy policy, we will notify you via email and post the updated privacy policy on the MobiLoans website. Please take note of the “Effective Date” at the top of this privacy policy. 

Why?

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do. 

What?

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include: 

  * Social Security number and income
  * Account balances and payment history
  * Credit history and credit scores

How? 

All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons MobiLoans, LLC chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing. 

For our everyday business purposes – such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus 

YES 

NO 

For our marketing purposes – to offer our products and services to you 

YES 

NO 

For joint marketing with other financial companies 

YES 

NO 

For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your transactions and experiences 

NO 

WE DO NOT SHARE 

For our affiliates everyday business purposes –  information about your creditworthiness 

NO 

WE DO NOT SHARE 

For our affiliates to market to you

NO 

WE DO NOT SHARE 

For non-affiliates to market to you

YES 

YES 

To limit our sharing

  * Call 877-836-1518 – our menu will prompt you through your choice(s);
  * Log in to your account at [www.mobiloans.com](http://www.mobiloans.com/) and click on the “Manage Profile” tab and select “Contact Preferences”; or
  * Contact us via email: [support@mobiloans.com](mailto:support@mobiloans.com).

Please note:  
If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information as soon as the same day that you apply for a line of credit. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.

However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing. 

How does MobiLoans, LLC protect my personal information?

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings. 

We also maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards (i.e., computer virus protection software, firewalls, 128 bit Secure Socket Layer). Only authorized employees have access. 

How does MobiLoans, LLC collect my personal information?

We collect your personal information, for example, when you 

  * Apply for a line of credit
  * Give us your income information
  * Provide employment information
  * Provide account information
  * Give us your contact information

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies. 

Why can’t I limit all sharing?

Federal law gives you the right to limit only 

  * Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes-information about your creditworthiness
  * Affiliates from using your information to market to you
  * Sharing for non-affiliates to market to you.

Affiliates

Financial and nonfinancial companies related by common ownership or control. 

  * MobiLoans, LLC has no affiliates.

Non-affiliates

Financial and nonfinancial companies not related by common ownership or control.

  * Non-affiliates we share with can include direct marketing companies for application resell, direct mail and other purposes.

Joint Marketing

A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you. 

  * Our joint marketing partners include financial institutions, credit card companies, partners that promote our products, pre-paid debit card providers and other lending companies. 

As part of our credit underwriting and information collection process, we will consider bank account information provided by you and we may detect additional bank accounts under your ownership. We also may collect and consider information about you from non-credit reporting agency data providers, including, for example, information about your location and the location of your mobile devices and publicly available information about you. 

Updating your information: If you need to update the personal information you have given us, log in to your account at [www.mobiloans.com](http://www.mobiloans.com/) and click on the “Manage Profile” tab and select “Edit Your Application” or call 877-836-1518 to speak to an account representative. 

“Do not track”: When someone visits the MobiLoans website, a cookie is placed on the visitor’s computer (if the visitor accepts cookies). The cookie we place on your computer does not contain any of your personally identifiable information. MobiLoans advertises its products and services on websites that you may visit, and MobiLoans uses service providers to place such advertisements. Those service providers (such as Google, Microsoft or Yahoo) may use cookies placed on your computer to show you advertisements for MobiLoans services on other websites. You can opt-out from service providers’ and/or marketers’ use of cookies in this manner by visiting each service provider’s advertising opt-out page or by utilizing “do not track” functionality in your web browser. If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the MobiLoans website, you will not be able to subscribe to the service offerings on the MobiLoans website. 

Changes to this privacy policy: If we make material changes to this privacy policy, we will notify you via email and post the updated privacy policy on the MobiLoans website. Please take note of the “Effective Date” at the top of this privacy policy.
